Narrator: Languages
Speaker: Do you think you’re good at learning languages?
Narrator: 2
Speaker: Is there anything about learning English that you’re bad at?
Narrator: 3
Speaker: Do you think listening to pop music is good for your English?
Narrator: 4
Speaker: Are you afraid of going to places where you don’t speak the language?
Narrator: 5
Speaker: What English-speaking countries are you most interested in?
Narrator: Tourism
Speaker: Which towns or cities in your country are full of tourists in the summer?
Narrator: 7
Speaker: What tourist attractions is your country famous for?
Narrator: 8
Speaker: Are people in your country usually nice to tourists?
Narrator: 9
Speaker: Do you get angry with tourists who don’t try to speak your language?
Narrator: 10
Speaker: Are people in your capital city very different from people in the rest of your country?